<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>byymyself</title>
    <link>https://flippedaben.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on byymyself</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 21:08:08 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://flippedaben.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Knowing Yourself</title>
      <link>https://flippedaben.github.io/posts/knowing-yourself/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 21:08:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://flippedaben.github.io/posts/knowing-yourself/</guid>
      <description>Context I watched a YouTube video about Destiny interviewing Dr. K. Near the end, Destiny asks Alok: what is the number one tip he would give to someone who wants to be more mentally healthy. The tip is to know yourself. Quoting Alok:
 Understand yourself in the same way your try to understand external things.
 I hadn&amp;rsquo;t really thought about it this way. The way I try to understand anything externally is through the scientific method (usually).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brother Left</title>
      <link>https://flippedaben.github.io/posts/brother-left/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2019 20:22:23 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://flippedaben.github.io/posts/brother-left/</guid>
      <description>Honesty
My brother crashed at my place for two to three months to finish an internship in Austin. Today, he left. On the way back home, from the airport, I could feel what every writer describes as the precursor to crying. Part of it is the throat swelling. Part of it is the eye closing.
I want to understand myself more, so I tried my best to be honest. I didn&amp;rsquo;t try to put on a tough act.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meta Nihilism</title>
      <link>https://flippedaben.github.io/posts/meta-nihilism/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 20:21:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://flippedaben.github.io/posts/meta-nihilism/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking about the meaningless of everything. The universe is inherently pointless. I think philosophers like to call it nihilism. I&amp;rsquo;ve heard people say that although it is a depressing thought, it is actually very uplifting. The main idea is that you get to create the meaning to your life. This is as liberating as it gets.
I read some Reddit comment a while back. I&amp;rsquo;m paraphrasing here:
 The next logical leap is to ask what nihilism says about nihilism.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
