<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
	<channel>
		<title>byy myself</title>
		<link>https://flippedaben.github.io</link>
		<atom:link href="https://flippedaben.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Snap</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;We went through round house, turn around kicks, both sides on paddle targets. I
focused on pivoting on the ball of my grounded foot and aiming. I feared hitting
the target, but I reminded myself. &lt;em&gt;I should trust myself. I should trust in my
body’s resilience.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I got to go twice before Master Ali moved on to a new drill. He had each holder
wear the vest of a sparring suit. We did a combination kick: power round house
into sliding round house. We tried for two hits to the solar plexus. He reminded
us that the harder I kicked, the harder the others would kick when it was my
turn to hold/wear. I kicked decently hard. When I held, I felt Ron’s and Alex’s
kicks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the middle, Master Ali stopped us and told us that our combination kicks were
slow. They should be fast, otherwise we might as well be practicing two separate
kicks. I focused on flow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sticking with the vest, we did three more combination kick drills. We did speed
round house into a jump speed roundhouse with the other leg. We did a similar
drill with power round house. Lastly, we did the previous drill except twice,
non-stop.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After stripping the vests, I learned roughly the first half of Basic Form 3 from
Lynn.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After some repetitions, Master Ali stopped us and held a wooden board. Brad also
held a board. Brad’s free hand formed a knife-hand, chambered three feet away
from the board, and slammed into the board. It broke in two.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then, Master Ali held up his board. With his free hand, he also formed a
knife-hand, but he chambered it only three inches from the board. The motion was
basically palm down to palm up and looked like a blur. It broke in two.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“See the difference?”, he asked. He told us to find how the movements in our
forms generated power. In a middle punch, we move the fist out, but near full
extension, we rotate the fist and snap. Sometimes it’s a big motion, but
sometimes, it’s in the snap.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2018 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
				<link>https://flippedaben.github.io/2018/01/18/tukong1/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flippedaben.github.io/2018/01/18/tukong1/</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
