<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on byymyself</title>
    <link>https://flippedaben.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on byymyself</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 08:14:51 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://flippedaben.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How I Back Squat</title>
      <link>https://flippedaben.github.io/posts/how-i-back-squat/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 08:14:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://flippedaben.github.io/posts/how-i-back-squat/</guid>
      <description>This is a description of how I back squat with a barbell. In this guide, we have a timeline of certain key events, which partition the squat into sections.
Before the squat  Breathe in and hold. Engage core (no anterior pelvic tilt). Chest up. Engage rear delts and upper back to retract shoulders. Unrack the bar.  Hold this upper body posture for the entirety of the movement.
Eccentric, part 1 Start the movement of your knees forward by engaging the tibialis muscles (located around the shin).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Remember to Relax</title>
      <link>https://flippedaben.github.io/posts/remember-to-relax/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 21:40:20 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://flippedaben.github.io/posts/remember-to-relax/</guid>
      <description>This post is about activities I do where it is natural to think of engaging muscles to achieve some end result. The other perspective is relaxing the muscles you don&amp;rsquo;t want to use. I didn&amp;rsquo;t think of it like that, until recently. For this to make sense, I&amp;rsquo;ll provide some context. Here is a timeline of events in which this idea popped up.
Timeline A single MMA class When I was to college, I went to a single training session hosted by the MMA club.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wim Hof Method Review</title>
      <link>https://flippedaben.github.io/posts/wim-hof-method-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 18:24:34 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://flippedaben.github.io/posts/wim-hof-method-review/</guid>
      <description>Intro I started the Wim Hof method on May 25, 2020. I did the cold showers and breathing exercises almost everyday. I did take a few days off due to sickness. I practiced meditation on and off.
Cons  You have to do it nearly everyday. Cold showers are uncomfortable at first. Breathing exercise is exercise, so you still have to put in the effort. It is also uncomfortable sometimes, as exercise is.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Knowing Yourself</title>
      <link>https://flippedaben.github.io/posts/knowing-yourself/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 21:08:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://flippedaben.github.io/posts/knowing-yourself/</guid>
      <description>Context I watched a YouTube video about Destiny interviewing Dr. K. Near the end, Destiny asks Alok: what is the number one tip he would give to someone who wants to be more mentally healthy. The tip is to know yourself. Quoting Alok:
 Understand yourself in the same way your try to understand external things.
 I hadn&amp;rsquo;t really thought about it this way. The way I try to understand anything externally is through the scientific method (usually).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cat in Car</title>
      <link>https://flippedaben.github.io/posts/cat-in-car/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 20:15:22 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://flippedaben.github.io/posts/cat-in-car/</guid>
      <description>Many dog walkers have passed by my car. Those who listened closely heard a faint meow. That&amp;rsquo;s because there was a little kitten inside the engine bay.
I decided to go grocery shopping one Saturday morning. When I sat down at the steering wheel, I saw a paper note slid beneath the wind shield wiper. I read a sloppy cursive that said a kitten was in my car. At first, I was confused.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brother Left</title>
      <link>https://flippedaben.github.io/posts/brother-left/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2019 20:22:23 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://flippedaben.github.io/posts/brother-left/</guid>
      <description>Honesty
My brother crashed at my place for two to three months to finish an internship in Austin. Today, he left. On the way back home, from the airport, I could feel what every writer describes as the precursor to crying.
I want to understand myself more, so I tried my best to be honest. I didn&amp;rsquo;t try to put on a tough act. Well, during the drive back home I did because I wanted to see the road clearly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meta Nihilism</title>
      <link>https://flippedaben.github.io/posts/meta-nihilism/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 20:21:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://flippedaben.github.io/posts/meta-nihilism/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking about the meaningless of everything. The universe is inherently pointless. I think philosophers like to call it nihilism. I&amp;rsquo;ve heard people say that although it is a depressing thought, it is actually very uplifting. The main idea is that you get to create the meaning to your life. This is as liberating as it gets.
I read some Reddit comment a while back. I&amp;rsquo;m paraphrasing here:
 The next logical leap is to ask what nihilism says about nihilism.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
